{
    "N5L1KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "山", "answer": "やま", "english_answer": "mountain" },
        { "question": "ふじ山", "answer": "ふじさん", "english_answer": "Mt. Fuji" },
        { "question": "登山", "answer": "とざん", "english_answer": "climbing" },
        { "question": "川", "answer": "かわ", "english_answer": "river" },
        { "question": "山川さん", "answer": "やまかわさん", "english_answer": "Mr./Ms. Yamakawa" },
        { "question": "インダス川", "answer": "インダスがわ", "english_answer": "the Indus River" },
        { "question": "田", "answer": "た", "english_answer": "rice field" },
        { "question": "山田さん", "answer": "やまださん", "english_answer": "Mr./Ms. Yamada" },
        { "question": "水田", "answer": "すいでん", "english_answer": "rice field" },
        { "question": "油田", "answer": "ゆでん", "english_answer": "oil field" },
        { "question": "日", "answer": "ひ", "english_answer": "the sun" },
        { "question": "日曜日", "answer": "にちようび", "english_answer": "Sunday" },
        { "question": "日本", "answer": "にほん", "english_answer": "Japan" },
        { "question": "休日", "answer": "きゅうじつ", "english_answer": "holiday" },
        { "question": "月", "answer": "つき", "english_answer": "the moon" },
        { "question": "月曜日", "answer": "げつようび", "english_answer": "Monday" },
        { "question": "１月", "answer": "いちがつ", "english_answer": "January" },
        { "question": "今月", "answer": "こんげつ", "english_answer": "this month" },
        { "question": "火", "answer": "ひ", "english_answer": "fire" },
        { "question": "火曜日", "answer": "かようび", "english_answer": "Tuesday" },
        { "question": "火山", "answer": "かざん", "english_answer": "volcano" },
        { "question": "火事", "answer": "かじ", "english_answer": "fire" },
        { "question": "水", "answer": "みず", "english_answer": "water" },
        { "question": "水曜日", "answer": "すいようび", "english_answer": "Wednesday" },
        { "question": "水道", "answer": "すいどう", "english_answer": "waterworks" },
        { "question": "木", "answer": "き", "english_answer": "tree" },
        { "question": "木曜日", "answer": "もくようび", "english_answer": "Thursday" },
        { "question": "お金", "answer": "おかね", "english_answer": "money" },
        { "question": "金", "answer": "きん", "english_answer": "gold" },
        { "question": "金曜日", "answer": "きんようび", "english_answer": "Friday" },
        { "question": "土", "answer": "つち", "english_answer": "soil, earth" },
        { "question": "土曜日", "answer": "どようび", "english_answer": "Saturday" },
        { "question": "土地", "answer": "とち", "english_answer": "land" }
    ],
    "N5L2KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "一つ", "answer": "ひとつ", "english_answer": "one (thing)" },
        { "question": "一月", "answer": "いちがつ", "english_answer": "January" },
        { "question": "一日（day of a month）", "answer": "ついたち", "english_answer": "the 1st day of a month" },
        { "question": "一日（period）", "answer": "いちにち", "english_answer": "one day" },
        { "question": "二つ", "answer": "ふたつ", "english_answer": "two (things)" },
        { "question": "二月", "answer": "にがつ", "english_answer": "February" },
        { "question": "二日", "answer": "ふつか", "english_answer": "the 2nd day of a month" },
        { "question": "二人", "answer": "ふたり", "english_answer": "two people" },
        { "question": "三つ", "answer": "みっつ", "english_answer": "three (things)" },
        { "question": "三月", "answer": "さんがつ", "english_answer": "March" },
        { "question": "三日", "answer": "みっか", "english_answer": "the 3rd day of a month" },
        { "question": "三角", "answer": "さんかく", "english_answer": "triangle" },
        { "question": "四", "answer": "よん", "english_answer": "four" },
        { "question": "四つ", "answer": "よっつ", "english_answer": "four (things)" },
        { "question": "四月", "answer": "しがつ", "english_answer": "April" },
        { "question": "四日", "answer": "よっか", "english_answer": "the 4th day of a month" },
        { "question": "五つ", "answer": "いつつ", "english_answer": "five (things)" },
        { "question": "五月", "answer": "ごがつ", "english_answer": "May" },
        { "question": "五日", "answer": "いつか", "english_answer": "the 5th day of a month" },
        { "question": "五円", "answer": "ごえん", "english_answer": "five yen" },
        { "question": "六つ", "answer": "むっつ", "english_answer": "six (things)" },
        { "question": "六月", "answer": "ろくがつ", "english_answer": "June" },
        { "question": "六日", "answer": "むいか", "english_answer": "the 6th day of a month" },
        { "question": "六本木", "answer": "ろっぽんぎ", "english_answer": "Roppongi" },
        { "question": "七", "answer": "なな", "english_answer": "seven" },
        { "question": "七つ", "answer": "ななつ", "english_answer": "seven (things)" },
        { "question": "七月", "answer": "しちがつ", "english_answer": "July" },
        { "question": "七日", "answer": "なのか", "english_answer": "the 7th day of a month" },
        { "question": "八つ", "answer": "やっつ", "english_answer": "eight (things)" },
        { "question": "八月", "answer": "はちがつ", "english_answer": "August" },
        { "question": "八日", "answer": "ようか", "english_answer": "the 8th day of a month" },
        { "question": "八百屋", "answer": "やおや", "english_answer": "vegetable shop" },
        { "question": "九つ", "answer": "ここのつ", "english_answer": "nine (things)" },
        { "question": "九月", "answer": "くがつ", "english_answer": "September" },
        { "question": "九日", "answer": "ここのか", "english_answer": "the 9th day of a month" },
        { "question": "九州", "answer": "きゅうしゅう", "english_answer": "Kyushu" },
        { "question": "十", "answer": "とお、じゅう", "english_answer": "ten" },
        { "question": "十月", "answer": "じゅうがつ", "english_answer": "October" },
        { "question": "十日", "answer": "とおか", "english_answer": "the 10th day of a month" },
        { "question": "十分な", "answer": "じゅうぶんな", "english_answer": "enough" }
    ],
    "N5L3KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "百", "answer": "ひゃく", "english_answer": "100" },
        { "question": "三百", "answer": "さんびゃく", "english_answer": "300" },
        { "question": "六百", "answer": "ろっぴゃく", "english_answer": "600" },
        { "question": "百科事典", "answer": "ひゃっかじてん", "english_answer": "encyclopedia" },
        { "question": "千", "answer": "せん", "english_answer": "1000" },
        { "question": "二千", "answer": "にせん", "english_answer": "2000" },
        { "question": "三千", "answer": "さんぜん", "english_answer": "3000" },
        { "question": "千葉県", "answer": "ちばけん", "english_answer": "Chiba Prefecture" },
        { "question": "万", "answer": "まん", "english_answer": "10000" },
        { "question": "一万", "answer": "いちまん", "english_answer": "10000" },
        { "question": "万国", "answer": "ばんこく", "english_answer": "all nations" },
        { "question": "万年筆", "answer": "まんねんひつ", "english_answer": "fountain pen" },
        { "question": "円", "answer": "えん", "english_answer": "yen, circle" },
        { "question": "四万円", "answer": "よんまんえん", "english_answer": "40000 yen" },
        { "question": "円高", "answer": "えんだか", "english_answer": "strong yen" },
        { "question": "年", "answer": "とし", "english_answer": "year, age" },
        { "question": "二千年", "answer": "にせんねん", "english_answer": "the year 2000" },
        { "question": "来年", "answer": "らいねん", "english_answer": "next year" },
        { "question": "年金", "answer": "ねんきん", "english_answer": "pension" },
        { "question": "上", "answer": "うえ", "english_answer": "above, on" },
        { "question": "上がる", "answer": "あがる", "english_answer": "to go up" },
        { "question": "水上スキー", "answer": "すいじょうスキー", "english_answer": "water-skiing" },
        { "question": "上着", "answer": "うわぎ", "english_answer": "jacket" },
        { "question": "下", "answer": "した", "english_answer": "under" },
        { "question": "下がる", "answer": "さがる", "english_answer": "to go down" },
        { "question": "上下", "answer": "じょうげ", "english_answer": "up and down" },
        { "question": "地下鉄", "answer": "ちかてつ", "english_answer": "subway" },
        { "question": "中", "answer": "なか", "english_answer": "inside" },
        { "question": "一日中", "answer": "いちにちじゅう", "english_answer": "all day (long)" },
        { "question": "中学", "answer": "ちゅうがく", "english_answer": "junior high school" },
        { "question": "中心", "answer": "ちゅうしん", "english_answer": "center" },
        { "question": "半年", "answer": "はんとし", "english_answer": "half a year" },
        { "question": "半分", "answer": "はんぶん", "english_answer": "half" },
        { "question": "四時半", "answer": "よじはん", "english_answer": "4:30" },
        { "question": "半日", "answer": "はんにち", "english_answer": "half a day" },
        { "question": "分ける", "answer": "わける", "english_answer": "to divide" },
        { "question": "分かる", "answer": "わかる", "english_answer": "to understand" },
        { "question": "１０分", "answer": "じゅうぷん", "english_answer": "10 minutes" },
        { "question": "十分", "answer": "じゅうぶん", "english_answer": "enough" }
    ],
    "N5L4KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "人", "answer": "ひと", "english_answer": "person" },
        { "question": "一人", "answer": "ひとり", "english_answer": "one person" },
        { "question": "三人", "answer": "さんにん", "english_answer": "three people" },
        { "question": "日本人", "answer": "にほんじん", "english_answer": "Japanese" },
        { "question": "子ども", "answer": "こども", "english_answer": "child" },
        { "question": "女子", "answer": "じょし", "english_answer": "female" },
        { "question": "親子", "answer": "おやこ", "english_answer": "parent and child" },
        { "question": "調子", "answer": "ちょうし", "english_answer": "condition" },
        { "question": "女の人", "answer": "おんなのひと", "english_answer": "woman" },
        { "question": "女の子", "answer": "おんなのこ", "english_answer": "girl" },
        { "question": "女性", "answer": "じょせい", "english_answer": "woman" },
        { "question": "男の子", "answer": "おとこのこ", "english_answer": "boy" },
        { "question": "男女", "answer": "だんじょ", "english_answer": "man and woman" },
        { "question": "長男", "answer": "ちょうなん", "english_answer": "eldest son" },
        { "question": "男性", "answer": "だんせい", "english_answer": "man" },
        { "question": "目", "answer": "め", "english_answer": "eye" },
        { "question": "一日目", "answer": "いちにちめ", "english_answer": "the first day" },
        { "question": "目薬", "answer": "めぐすり", "english_answer": "eye lotion" },
        { "question": "目的", "answer": "もくてき", "english_answer": "purpose" },
        { "question": "口", "answer": "くち", "english_answer": "mouth" },
        { "question": "入口", "answer": "いりぐち", "english_answer": "entrance" },
        { "question": "人口", "answer": "じんこう", "english_answer": "population" },
        { "question": "非常口", "answer": "ひじょうぐち", "english_answer": "emergency exit" },
        { "question": "耳", "answer": "みみ", "english_answer": "ear" },
        { "question": "耳鼻科", "answer": "じびか", "english_answer": "N.E.T. clinic" },
        { "question": "手", "answer": "て", "english_answer": "hand" },
        { "question": "上手な", "answer": "じょうずな", "english_answer": "skillful" },
        { "question": "下手な", "answer": "へたな", "english_answer": "unskillful" },
        { "question": "手紙", "answer": "てがみ", "english_answer": "letter" },
        { "question": "足", "answer": "あし", "english_answer": "leg" },
        { "question": "一足", "answer": "いっそく", "english_answer": "a pair (of shoes)" },
        { "question": "足りる", "answer": "たりる", "english_answer": "to be enough" },
        { "question": "遠足", "answer": "えんそく", "english_answer": "excursion" },
        { "question": "力", "answer": "ちから", "english_answer": "power" },
        { "question": "水力", "answer": "すいりょく", "english_answer": "water power" },
        { "question": "体力", "answer": "たいりょく", "english_answer": "physical strength" }
    ],
    "N5L5KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "父", "answer": "ちち", "english_answer": "father" },
        { "question": "お父さん", "answer": "おとうさん", "english_answer": "father" },
        { "question": "父親", "answer": "ちちおや", "english_answer": "father" },
        { "question": "母", "answer": "はは", "english_answer": "mother" },
        { "question": "お母さん", "answer": "おかあさん", "english_answer": "mother" },
        { "question": "父母", "answer": "ふぼ", "english_answer": "parents" },
        { "question": "母国", "answer": "ぼこく", "english_answer": "mother country" },
        { "question": "先", "answer": "さき", "english_answer": "future, ahead" },
        { "question": "先月", "answer": "せんげつ", "english_answer": "last month" },
        { "question": "先輩", "answer": "せんぱい", "english_answer": "senior" },
        { "question": "生まれる", "answer": "うまれる", "english_answer": "to be born" },
        { "question": "先生", "answer": "せんせい", "english_answer": "teacher" },
        { "question": "生きる", "answer": "いきる", "english_answer": "to live" },
        { "question": "生活", "answer": "せいかつ", "english_answer": "life" },
        { "question": "学生", "answer": "がくせい", "english_answer": "student" },
        { "question": "大学", "answer": "だいがく", "english_answer": "university" },
        { "question": "科学", "answer": "かがく", "english_answer": "science" },
        { "question": "留学する", "answer": "りゅうがくする", "english_answer": "to study abroad" },
        { "question": "学校", "answer": "がっこう", "english_answer": "school" },
        { "question": "校長", "answer": "こうちょう", "english_answer": "school master" },
        { "question": "小学校", "answer": "しょうがっこう", "english_answer": "primary school" },
        { "question": "母校", "answer": "ぼこう", "english_answer": "alma mater" },
        { "question": "友だち", "answer": "ともだち", "english_answer": "friend" },
        { "question": "友人", "answer": "ゆうじん", "english_answer": "friend" },
        { "question": "親友", "answer": "しんゆう", "english_answer": "close friend" },
        { "question": "本", "answer": "ほん", "english_answer": "book" },
        { "question": "日本", "answer": "にほん、にっぽん", "english_answer": "Japan" },
        { "question": "本屋", "answer": "ほんや", "english_answer": "book shop" },
        { "question": "山本さん", "answer": "やまもとさん", "english_answer": "Mr. Yamamoto" },
        { "question": "毎日", "answer": "まいにち", "english_answer": "every day" },
        { "question": "毎月", "answer": "まいつき", "english_answer": "every month" },
        { "question": "毎年", "answer": "まいとし、まいねん", "english_answer": "every year" },
        { "question": "毎朝", "answer": "まいあさ", "english_answer": "every morning" },
        { "question": "何", "answer": "なに", "english_answer": "what" },
        { "question": "何月", "answer": "なんがつ", "english_answer": "what month" },
        { "question": "何人", "answer": "なんにん", "english_answer": "how many people" },
        { "question": "何時", "answer": "なんじ", "english_answer": "what time" }
    ],
    "N5L6KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "前", "answer": "まえ", "english_answer": "the front" },
        { "question": "三日前", "answer": "みっかまえ", "english_answer": "three days ago" },
        { "question": "前半", "answer": "ぜんはん", "english_answer": "the first half" },
        { "question": "後", "answer": "あと", "english_answer": "after, later" },
        { "question": "後ろ", "answer": "うしろ", "english_answer": "back, behind" },
        { "question": "前後", "answer": "ぜんご", "english_answer": "back and forth" },
        { "question": "最後", "answer": "さいご", "english_answer": "the last" },
        { "question": "外", "answer": "そと", "english_answer": "outside" },
        { "question": "外国", "answer": "がいこく", "english_answer": "foreign country" },
        { "question": "左", "answer": "ひだり", "english_answer": "left" },
        { "question": "左手", "answer": "ひだりて", "english_answer": "lefthand" },
        { "question": "左側", "answer": "ひだりがわ", "english_answer": "left side" },
        { "question": "右", "answer": "みぎ", "english_answer": "right" },
        { "question": "右手", "answer": "みぎて", "english_answer": "righthand" },
        { "question": "左右", "answer": "さゆう", "english_answer": "left and right" },
        { "question": "右側", "answer": "みぎがわ", "english_answer": "right side" },
        { "question": "東", "answer": "ひがし", "english_answer": "east" },
        { "question": "東口", "answer": "ひがしぐち", "english_answer": "the east gate" },
        { "question": "東京", "answer": "とうきょう", "english_answer": "Tokyo" },
        { "question": "東洋", "answer": "とうよう", "english_answer": "the Orient" },
        { "question": "西", "answer": "にし", "english_answer": "west" },
        { "question": "西口", "answer": "にしぐち", "english_answer": "the west gate" },
        { "question": "東西", "answer": "とうざい", "english_answer": "east and west" },
        { "question": "西洋", "answer": "せいよう", "english_answer": "the West" },
        { "question": "南", "answer": "みなみ", "english_answer": "south" },
        { "question": "南口", "answer": "みなみぐち", "english_answer": "the south gate" },
        { "question": "東南アジア", "answer": "とうなんアジア", "english_answer": "Southeast Asia" },
        { "question": "南極", "answer": "なんきょく", "english_answer": "South Pole" },
        { "question": "北", "answer": "きた", "english_answer": "north" },
        { "question": "北口", "answer": "きたぐち", "english_answer": "the north gate" },
        { "question": "南北", "answer": "なんぼく", "english_answer": "north and south" },
        { "question": "北海道", "answer": "ほっかいどう", "english_answer": "Hokkaido" },
        { "question": "名前", "answer": "なまえ", "english_answer": "name" },
        { "question": "十名", "answer": "じゅうめい", "english_answer": "10 people" },
        { "question": "有名", "answer": "ゆうめい", "english_answer": "famous" },
        { "question": "人名", "answer": "じんめい", "english_answer": "a person's name" }
    ],
    "N5L7KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "牛", "answer": "うし", "english_answer": "cow" },
        { "question": "水牛", "answer": "すいぎゅう", "english_answer": "buffalo" },
        { "question": "牛肉", "answer": "ぎゅうにく", "english_answer": "beef" },
        { "question": "牛乳", "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう", "english_answer": "cow's milk" },
        { "question": "馬", "answer": "うま", "english_answer": "horse" },
        { "question": "馬車", "answer": "ばしゃ", "english_answer": "carriage" },
        { "question": "トロイの木馬", "answer": "トロイのもくば", "english_answer": "Trojan horse" },
        { "question": "乗馬", "answer": "じょうば", "english_answer": "horse riding" },
        { "question": "魚", "answer": "さかな", "english_answer": "fish" },
        { "question": "金魚", "answer": "きんぎょ", "english_answer": "goldfish" },
        { "question": "人魚", "answer": "にんぎょ", "english_answer": "mermaid" },
        { "question": "貝", "answer": "かい", "english_answer": "shellfish" },
        { "question": "貝がら", "answer": "かいがら", "english_answer": "shell" },
        { "question": "雨", "answer": "あめ", "english_answer": "rain" },
        { "question": "大雨", "answer": "おおあめ", "english_answer": "heavy rain" },
        { "question": "雨期", "answer": "うき", "english_answer": "rainy season" },
        { "question": "天", "answer": "てん", "english_answer": "heaven" },
        { "question": "天気", "answer": "てんき", "english_answer": "weather" },
        { "question": "天国", "answer": "てんごく", "english_answer": "paradise" },
        { "question": "天気", "answer": "てんき", "english_answer": "weather" },
        { "question": "人気", "answer": "にんき", "english_answer": "popularity" },
        { "question": "気をつける", "answer": "きをつける", "english_answer": "to take care" },
        { "question": "気持ち", "answer": "きもち", "english_answer": "feeling" },
        { "question": "車", "answer": "くるま", "english_answer": "car" },
        { "question": "電車", "answer": "でんしゃ", "english_answer": "train" },
        { "question": "自動車", "answer": "じどうしゃ", "english_answer": "automobile" },
        { "question": "門", "answer": "もん", "english_answer": "gate" },
        { "question": "正門", "answer": "せいもん", "english_answer": "main gate" },
        { "question": "専門", "answer": "せんもん", "english_answer": "major field of study" },
        { "question": "午前", "answer": "ごぜん", "english_answer": "(in the) morning" },
        { "question": "午後", "answer": "ごご", "english_answer": "(in the) afternoon" }
    ],
    "N5L8KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "大きい", "answer": "おおきい", "english_answer": "big" },
        { "question": "大学", "answer": "だいがく", "english_answer": "university" },
        { "question": "アジア大会", "answer": "アジアたいかい", "english_answer": "Asian Games" },
        { "question": "大人", "answer": "おとな", "english_answer": "adult" },
        { "question": "小さい", "answer": "ちいさい", "english_answer": "small" },
        { "question": "小川", "answer": "おがわ", "english_answer": "small stream" },
        { "question": "小学校", "answer": "しょうがっこう", "english_answer": "primary school" },
        { "question": "小犬", "answer": "こいぬ", "english_answer": "puppy" },
        { "question": "高い", "answer": "たかい", "english_answer": "high, expensive" },
        { "question": "高校生", "answer": "こうこうせい", "english_answer": "high school student" },
        { "question": "円高", "answer": "えんだか", "english_answer": "strong yen" },
        { "question": "安い", "answer": "やすい", "english_answer": "cheap" },
        { "question": "安心する", "answer": "あんしんする", "english_answer": "to be relieved" },
        { "question": "安全", "answer": "あんぜん", "english_answer": "safety" },
        { "question": "新しい", "answer": "あたらしい", "english_answer": "new" },
        { "question": "新聞", "answer": "しんぶん", "english_answer": "newspaper" },
        { "question": "新人", "answer": "しんじん", "english_answer": "newcomer" },
        { "question": "新年", "answer": "しんねん", "english_answer": "new year" },
        { "question": "古い", "answer": "ふるい", "english_answer": "old" },
        { "question": "中古車", "answer": "ちゅうこしゃ", "english_answer": "used car" },
        { "question": "長い", "answer": "ながい", "english_answer": "long" },
        { "question": "社長", "answer": "しゃちょう", "english_answer": "company president" },
        { "question": "学長", "answer": "がくちょう", "english_answer": "university president" },
        { "question": "校長", "answer": "こうちょう", "english_answer": "school principal" },
        { "question": "多い", "answer": "おおい", "english_answer": "many, much" },
        { "question": "多少", "answer": "たしょう", "english_answer": "a little" },
        { "question": "多数決", "answer": "たすうけつ", "english_answer": "decision by majority" },
        { "question": "少ない", "answer": "すくない", "english_answer": "few, little" },
        { "question": "少し", "answer": "すこし", "english_answer": "a few, a little" },
        { "question": "少年", "answer": "しょうねん", "english_answer": "boys" },
        { "question": "少女", "answer": "しょうじょ", "english_answer": "girl" },
        { "question": "早い", "answer": "はやい", "english_answer": "early" },
        { "question": "早朝", "answer": "そうちょう", "english_answer": "early morning" },
        { "question": "早送り", "answer": "はやおくり", "english_answer": "fast forward" }
    ],
    "N5L9KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "行く", "answer": "いく", "english_answer": "to go" },
        { "question": "行き方", "answer": "いきかた", "english_answer": "how to get to place" },
        { "question": "銀行", "answer": "ぎんこう", "english_answer": "bank" },
        { "question": "三行目", "answer": "さんぎょうめ", "english_answer": "the third line" },
        { "question": "来る", "answer": "くる", "english_answer": "to come" },
        { "question": "来年", "answer": "らいねん", "english_answer": "next year" },
        { "question": "来週", "answer": "らいしゅう", "english_answer": "next week" },
        { "question": "将来", "answer": "しょうらい", "english_answer": "future" },
        { "question": "食べる", "answer": "たべる", "english_answer": "to eat" },
        { "question": "外食する", "answer": "がいしょくする", "english_answer": "to eat out" },
        { "question": "食料品", "answer": "しょくりょうひん", "english_answer": "grocery" },
        { "question": "食堂", "answer": "しょくどう", "english_answer": "dining hall" },
        { "question": "見る", "answer": "みる", "english_answer": "to see, to look at" },
        { "question": "見せる", "answer": "みせる", "english_answer": "to show" },
        { "question": "見学する", "answer": "けんがくする", "english_answer": "to visit for study" },
        { "question": "意見", "answer": "いけん", "english_answer": "opinion" },
        { "question": "入る", "answer": "はいる", "english_answer": "to enter" },
        { "question": "入れる", "answer": "いれる", "english_answer": "to put in" },
        { "question": "入口", "answer": "いりぐち", "english_answer": "entrance" },
        { "question": "入学する", "answer": "にゅうがくする", "english_answer": "to enter a school" },
        { "question": "出る", "answer": "でる", "english_answer": "to go/come out" },
        { "question": "出す", "answer": "だす", "english_answer": "to take out" },
        { "question": "出口", "answer": "でぐち", "english_answer": "exit" },
        { "question": "出席する", "answer": "しゅっせきする", "english_answer": "to attend" },
        { "question": "立つ", "answer": "たつ", "english_answer": "to stand" },
        { "question": "立食", "answer": "りっしょく", "english_answer": "buffet party" },
        { "question": "国立大学", "answer": "こくりつだいがく", "english_answer": "national university" },
        { "question": "書く", "answer": "かく", "english_answer": "to write" },
        { "question": "読書", "answer": "どくしょ", "english_answer": "reading books" },
        { "question": "下書き", "answer": "したがき", "english_answer": "draft" },
        { "question": "辞書", "answer": "じしょ", "english_answer": "dictionary" },
        { "question": "言う", "answer": "いう", "english_answer": "to say" },
        { "question": "言語", "answer": "げんご", "english_answer": "language" },
        { "question": "伝言", "answer": "でんごん", "english_answer": "message" },
        { "question": "飲む", "answer": "のむ", "english_answer": "to drink" },
        { "question": "飲み物", "answer": "のみもの", "english_answer": "beverage" },
        { "question": "飲食店", "answer": "いんしょくてん", "english_answer": "restaurants" }
    ],
    "N5L10KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "話す", "answer": "はなす", "english_answer": "to speak/talk" },
        { "question": "話", "answer": "はなし", "english_answer": "story" },
        { "question": "電話", "answer": "でんわ", "english_answer": "telephone" },
        { "question": "会話", "answer": "かいわ", "english_answer": "conversation" },
        { "question": "読む", "answer": "よむ", "english_answer": "to read" },
        { "question": "読書", "answer": "どくしょ", "english_answer": "reading books" },
        { "question": "日本語", "answer": "にほんご", "english_answer": "Japanese language" },
        { "question": "中国語", "answer": "ちゅうごくご", "english_answer": "Chinese language" },
        { "question": "外国語", "answer": "がいこくご", "english_answer": "foreign language" },
        { "question": "間", "answer": "あいだ", "english_answer": "between" },
        { "question": "時間", "answer": "じかん", "english_answer": "time" },
        { "question": "一年間", "answer": "いちねんかん", "english_answer": "(for) a year" },
        { "question": "間に合う", "answer": "まにあう", "english_answer": "to be in time" },
        { "question": "聞く", "answer": "きく", "english_answer": "to listen to" },
        { "question": "聞こえる", "answer": "きこえる", "english_answer": "can be heard" },
        { "question": "新聞", "answer": "しんぶん", "english_answer": "newspaper" },
        { "question": "買う", "answer": "かう", "english_answer": "to buy" },
        { "question": "買い物する", "answer": "かいものする", "english_answer": "to shop" },
        { "question": "売買する", "answer": "ばいばいする", "english_answer": "to buy and sell" },
        { "question": "休む", "answer": "やすむ", "english_answer": "to rest" },
        { "question": "休み", "answer": "やすみ", "english_answer": "holiday" },
        { "question": "休日", "answer": "きゅうじつ", "english_answer": "holiday" },
        { "question": "夏休み", "answer": "なつやすみ", "english_answer": "summer vacation" },
        { "question": "時", "answer": "とき", "english_answer": "time, when" },
        { "question": "４時", "answer": "よじ", "english_answer": "4 o'clock" },
        { "question": "１時間", "answer": "いちじかん", "english_answer": "one hour" },
        { "question": "時計", "answer": "とけい", "english_answer": "clock, watch" },
        { "question": "一週間", "answer": "いっしゅうかん", "english_answer": "one week" },
        { "question": "来週", "answer": "らいしゅう", "english_answer": "next week" },
        { "question": "先週", "answer": "せんしゅう", "english_answer": "last week" },
        { "question": "今週", "answer": "こんしゅう", "english_answer": "this week" },
        { "question": "道", "answer": "みち", "english_answer": "street, road, way" },
        { "question": "車道", "answer": "しゃどう", "english_answer": "roadway" },
        { "question": "水道", "answer": "すいどう", "english_answer": "waterworks" },
        { "question": "書道", "answer": "しょどう", "english_answer": "calligraphy" }
    ],
    "N5L11KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "今", "answer": "いま", "english_answer": "now" },
        { "question": "今月", "answer": "こんげつ", "english_answer": "this month" },
        { "question": "今年", "answer": "ことし", "english_answer": "this year" },
        { "question": "今日", "answer": "きょう", "english_answer": "today" },
        { "question": "会う", "answer": "あう", "english_answer": "to meet" },
        { "question": "会話", "answer": "かいわ", "english_answer": "conversation" },
        { "question": "新年会", "answer": "しんねんかい", "english_answer": "New Year's party" },
        { "question": "会議", "answer": "かいぎ", "english_answer": "meeting" },
        { "question": "社会", "answer": "しゃかい", "english_answer": "society" },
        { "question": "会社", "answer": "かいしゃ", "english_answer": "company" },
        { "question": "社長", "answer": "しゃちょう", "english_answer": "president" },
        { "question": "神社", "answer": "じんじゃ", "english_answer": "shrine" },
        { "question": "店", "answer": "みせ", "english_answer": "shop" },
        { "question": "店員", "answer": "てんいん", "english_answer": "sales person" },
        { "question": "売店", "answer": "ばいてん", "english_answer": "stand" },
        { "question": "駅", "answer": "えき", "english_answer": "station" },
        { "question": "駅長", "answer": "えきちょう", "english_answer": "stationmaster" },
        { "question": "駅前", "answer": "えきまえ", "english_answer": "around the station" },
        { "question": "花", "answer": "はな", "english_answer": "flower" },
        { "question": "花見", "answer": "はなみ", "english_answer": "cherry-blossom viewing" },
        { "question": "花火", "answer": "はなび", "english_answer": "firework" },
        { "question": "花屋", "answer": "はなや", "english_answer": "florist" },
        { "question": "国", "answer": "くに", "english_answer": "country, nation" },
        { "question": "外国", "answer": "がいこく", "english_answer": "foreign country" },
        { "question": "中国", "answer": "ちゅうごく", "english_answer": "China" },
        { "question": "国際会議", "answer": "こくさいかいぎ", "english_answer": "international conference" },
        { "question": "白い", "answer": "しろい", "english_answer": "white" },
        { "question": "白書", "answer": "はくしょ", "english_answer": "official paper" },
        { "question": "真っ白", "answer": "まっしろ", "english_answer": "snow white" },
        { "question": "空", "answer": "そら", "english_answer": "sky" },
        { "question": "空気", "answer": "くうき", "english_answer": "air" },
        { "question": "大空", "answer": "おおぞら", "english_answer": "big sky" },
        { "question": "空港", "answer": "くうこう", "english_answer": "airport" },
        { "question": "電車", "answer": "でんしゃ", "english_answer": "train" },
        { "question": "電話", "answer": "でんわ", "english_answer": "telephone" },
        { "question": "電気", "answer": "でんき", "english_answer": "electricity, light" },
        { "question": "電池", "answer": "でんち", "english_answer": "battery" }
    ]
}